Try 10 plus products from Kit Sanon's
brand hyphen. And here's what I think
are the hits, the misses, and everything
in between. Okay, so their super thick
milky toner is definitely a hit. This is
filled with ceramides and is mega
hydration in a bottle. Also a hit are
their peptide cocktail serums and their
retinol serum. Both affordable and
effective on anti-aging. And their
ceramide pillow cream. Oh my god, an
incredible night cream for dry skin. Now
coming to the almost. I think their
golden glow sunscreen does give a glowy
effect to the skin, but it has a slight
orange tint which may not work for some
skin tones. And their ice tank mask is a
very unique product to cool the skin,
but the menthol in it does tingle the
skin a little, but I have to say their
lip balms are sadly a miss for me. I
like the shade range that they have, but
I feel the formula on its own is too
runny and not thick enough to keep my
lips moisturized for a long time. And
I'm not a fan of the artificial sweet
taste that they have. But if you're new
to Hyphen, I think these four products
are incredible.